Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
circa 1974-1992
Gregg Smith Singers
90 linear ft.
Recordings of the Gregg Smith Singers, an American choral group founded in 1955. Recordings include contemporary choral works, opera music, Christmas specials, more.
3298881
Biographical History
The Gregg Smith Singers were founded by Gregg Smith in 1955, who remains their director, program designer and conductor today (2011). The group's mission, as articulated on their website, is "to encourage the development and preservation of American choral music, with an emphasis on new works of the 20th and 21st centuries, through performances, recordings, workshops and publications."
The Gregg Smith Singers have won numerous awards over the course of their career, and are internationally known for their intepretations of contemporary music and performances of works by living composers. The group had a strong working relationship with Igor Stravinsky for more than a decade and performed at his funeral. Among other achievements, in 1973 the group initiated both a New York City concert series and the Adirondack Festival of American Music (AFAM) in Saranac Lake, N.Y., both of which continue today (2011). They have won three Grammy Awards, two Montreux Awards, and the Stereo Review 1966 Record of the Year award for their Columbia recording of the music of the Revolutionary American composer, William Billings. Gregg Smith has also received a number of individual awards recognizing his contribution to the field of American choral music.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Gregg Smith Singers Recordings consists of memorabilia and recordings.
Memorabilia contains clippings, programs, publicity, and other assorted material pertaining to the group and their performances.
Recordings contains more than 900 reel-to-reel audiorecordings. Titles given in the inventory below are exactly as written on the items. The group's sound engineer often gave humorous titles to the tapes; for example, a recording of the group at Saranac might be titled "Smithanac" and a recording of Rosalind Rees and Ned Rorem might be titled "RozRem." ID numbers (e.g., "gss_075") have been assigned by staff. Please request items using both title and ID number.
Arrangement of the Collection
Recordings are arranged in numeric order by ID number, but are listed alphabetically in the inventory below.
Other Related Finding Aids
A full discography in PDF format is available on the Gregg Smith Singers website.
Subject and Genre Headings
Music; New York State; Smith, Gregg.; Gregg Smith Singers.; Gregg Smith Vocal Quartet.; Choruses, Secular (Mixed voices); Composers -- United States.; Choral conductors -- United States.; Music -- United States -- 20th century.; Choral music -- 20th century; Sound recordings.; Tape reels.; Singers.; Conductors.
Access Restrictions
The media for this collection has been processed. Access to recordings requires advance notice to create a use copy.
The remainder of the collection is currently unprocessed and not available for research. Please contact for more information
Acquisition Information
Gift of Gregg Smith, 2011.
Inventory
- Memorabilia
  - [in progress]
    This portion of the collection is not yet processed and is not open to researchers at this time.
- Recordings
  - Adiroz (3): "Mlle. Modiste"; Silent Night, gss_490; This is a compilation reel. Note on the reel reads: "Luboff". Note on the box reads: "Large stand 5 2/3 racks from XLR female in stage".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    1402-1406: "When the cat's away the mice will play" from "Mlle. Modiste" (chorus, orchestra); 1501-1505: "Joy to the World" (chorus); 1506-1511: "The First Noel" (chorus, tenor, soprano); 1601-1604: "O come all Ye faithful (chorus, soprano); 1701-1703: "Heard the Herald angels sing" (chorus, soprano); 1704-1708: "O little town of Bethlehem (quartet, chorus); 1709-1713/1801: "O little town of Bethlehem (quartet, chorus, tenor); 1802-1806: "We wish you a Merry Christmas" (chorus); 1807-1812: "The Boar's head" (chorus and bass); 1813/1901-1903/1906-1907: "I saw 3 ships" (chorus, tenor, soprano); 1904-1905: "I saw 3 ships" (chorus); 1908-1911/2001-2009: "I saw 3 ships" (mixed chorus, orchestra); 2010: "here we come Wassailing" (tenor, soprano, orchestra, bass); 2011: "Boar's Head" (tenor, soprano, orchestra, bass); 1908-2008: "Christmas Medley" - 1 - (Latin); 2 - "Jingle Bells"; 3 - "We Wish You a Merry Christmas"; 2012: "Wassail song"
  - Adiroz (4); Xmas [Christmas], gss_691; Note on the box reads: "Xmas takes; "Moss Cheapie"; "Modiste".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Adiroz (5): Mll. Modiste; Silent Night, gss_489; Compilation reel. "Mlle. Modiste" is an operetta in two acts composed by Victor Herbert.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    2707: "Mlle Modiste' (chorus and Orchestra); 2801-2805: "The time the place and the girl" (tenor and orchestra with chorus); 2806-2906/3001-3002: "If i were on the stage" (Kiss me again) (Roz - soprano and orchestra); 3003-3004/3102-3102: "The Dear little girl who is good" (bass with orchestra and chorus); 3103-3104: "Silent night" (chorus); 3105-3108/3201-3202: "Silent night" (chorus and soprano); 3203-3209/3301-3304: "On Parade" from "Sweethearts" (soprano, orchestra, chorus); 3305-3307: Entre act "Mlle Modiste', scene 2
  - Adiroz (6): I want what I want when I want (VH) [Victor Herbert], gss_463; Recording of "I want what I want when I want it" by Victor Herbert's "Mlle. Modiste" with orchestra and baritone.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    601-604: "I want what I want when I want it" by Victor Herbert's "Mlle. Modiste" (orchestra, baritone)
  - Adiroz (6): Mme. Modiste; Keokuk, Opening Chorus, gss_488; Compilation reel. "Mlle. Modiste" is an operetta in two acts composed by Victor Herbert.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    2601: "Mlle. Modiste", Victor Hubert (chorus and orchestra); 2602-2604/2705-2707: Opening chorus, Victor Herbert (chorus and orchestra); 2701-2704: "Waltz", Victor Hubert (chorus and orchestra); 3401-3403: "The Keokuk Culture Club", Victor Hubert (chorus and soprano)
  - Adiroz (7) (VH) [Victor Herbert], gss_464; Recording of Victor Herbert's music: Overture to "Mlle. Modiste" with orchestra.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    701-706: Victor Herbert's music: Overture to "Mlle. Modeste" (orchestra)
  - Adiroz (8) (VH) [Victor Herbert]: Kiss me, gss_465; Recording of Victor Herbert's music: Overture to "Mlle. Modiste" with orchestra.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    Cont'd from 464: 801-803/805: "Kiss me again" from "Mill. Modiste" (orchestra)
  - Adiroz (13) [Aaron] Copland; ED [Emily Dickinson]: Last song, gss_466; Recording of "Because I could not stop for Death" poem by Emily Dickinson, performed by Roz, soprano and orchestra, music by Aaron Copland.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    1301-1306: "Because I could not stop for Death" poem by Emily Dickinson (orchestra, soprano - Roz)
  - Adiroz (14), gss_143; 4 1/2; 1402 VH; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
  - Adiroz (26) VH [Victor Herbert], gss_467; Recording of Victor Herbert's music performed by orchestra and chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    2601-2604: Victor Herbert's music (orchestra, chorus)
  - Adiroz (27) VH [Victor Herbert], gss_468; Recording of Victor Herbert's music from "Mlle Modiste" performed by orchestra and chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    Cont'd from 467: 2701-2707: (orchestra, chorus); 2708: "I wonder if cupid is silly or stupid"; "For the time may be morning or evening"; "The time, the place and the girl" from "Mlle Modiste" (tenor solo, chorus)
  - Adiroz (28) VH [Victor Herbert]: Kiss me again; The time way, gss_469; Recording of Victor Herbert's music from "Mlle Modiste" with orchestra, tenor, chorus and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    Cont'd from 468: 2801-2805: (orchestra); 2802: "The time, the place and the girl" from "Mlle Modiste" (orchestra, tenor, chorus); 2806: "If I were on the stage" "Kiss me again" from "Mlle Modiste"
  - Adiroz (29) VH [Victor Herbert]: Kiss me again, gss_470; Recording of Victor Herbert's music from "Mlle Modiste" with orchestra and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    Cont'd from 469: 2901-2906: "If I were on the stage" "Kiss me again" from "Mlle Modiste" (orchestra, soprano)
  - Adiroz (30) VH [Victor Herbert], gss_471; Recording of Victor Herbert's music from "Mlle Modiste" and "The tattooed man" with orchestra, soprano and bass.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    Cont'd from 470: 3001-3002:If I were on the stage" "Kiss me again" from "Mlle Modiste" (orchestra, soprano); 3003-3004: "Boys will be boys, girls will be gilds" from "The tattooed man" (orchestra, bass)
  - Adiroz (31) VH [Victor Herbert], gss_472; Recording of Victor Herbert's music from "The tattooed man" with bass, orchestra, soprano and chorus and "Silent night" by Heinz Karl Gruber with chorus, soprano solo.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    Cont'd from 471: 3101-3102: "Boys will be boys, girls will be girls" (bass with orchestra, chorus); 3103-3104/3106-3108: "Silent night" by Heinz Karl Gruber(chorus, soprano solo)
  - Adiroz (32); Xmas [Christmas]: Silent night; VH [Victor Herbert], gss_473; Recording of "Silent night" by Heinz Karl Gruber with chorus, soprano solo and Victor Herbert's music from "Sweetheart" with orchestra, soprano, chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    Cont'd from 472: 3201-3202: "Silent night" (chorus, solo soprano); 3203-3209: "On parade" from "Sweethearts" by Victor Herbert (orchestra, soprano, chorus)
  - Adiroz (33) VH [Victor Herbert], gss_474; Recording of Victor Herbert's music from "Sweetheart" with orchestra, soprano, chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 37)
    Cont'd from 473: 3301-3304: "On parade" from "Sweethearts" by Victor Herbert (orchestra, soprano, chorus); 3305-3307: Act 2 from "Sweethearts" by Victor Herbert
  - Adiroz (34) VH [Victor Herbert]: Keeokuk, gss_475; Recording of Victor Herbert's music from "Mlle Modiste" with orchestra, soprano, chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    3401-3403: "The Keokuk Culture Club" from "Mlle. Modiste" by Victor Herbert (orchestra, soprano, chorus); 3404-3405: "Deck the halls" (chorus, small orchestra)
  - Aesop, gss_423; Recording of chorus, soprano, tenors, bass, piano performances.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    1801: "Amen... amen... amen..." (soprano, chorus, tenor, piano); 1802-1805: "Cock a doodle doo..." (soprano, chorus, bass, piano); 1806-1807: "So the foolish as..." (bass, piano, tenor; 1808: (tenor, soprano)
  - Aesop (1), gss_406; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (2), gss_407; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (3), gss_408; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (4), gss_409; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 180:00 (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (5), gss_410; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (6), gss_411; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (7), gss_412; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (8), gss_413; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (9), gss_414; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (10), gss_415; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (11), gss_416; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (12), gss_417; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (13), gss_418; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (14), gss_419; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (15), gss_420; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (16), gss_421; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - Aesop (17), gss_422; Most likely this is a recording of "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 60)
  - [Henry] Ainsworth etc. (1), gss_790; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    101-105: Ainsworth; 108-109/201-205: Cambridge 4 versions; 206-211: North field; 212-213/301-302: Bunker Hill; 303-304: Behold; 305: missing
  - [Henry] Ainsworth etc. (2), gss_791; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    306: Behold; 404-409 Lord Descended; 505: Ainsworth solos
  - [Henry] Ainsworth etc. (2) Edited, gss_840; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Henry] Ainsworth etc. (3), gss_792; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    603-605/701: 19th Psalm; Seasons; 702-705: Winter; Seasons: 705-708: Summer; 709-713: Spring mp-mp-pp; 714-715/801: Spring mf-mp-f; 802: Spring f-mp-f; 803: Spring f-f-p
  - [Henry] Ainsworth etc. (4), gss_839; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
    Seasons: 804-805: Autumn
  - Ainsworth (1): Gregg Smith Singers - The Founding years, Side 1, gss_600; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
    Band 1: Psalms 100, 25, 1, 111, 97 (chorus and 2 songs); Band 2: Psalms 55, 34, 13, 27, 18, 75 (solo quartet); Band 3: Psalms; Band 4: Psalms: 4 and 23; Band 5: Bay Psalms 95, 39, 100
  - Ainsworth (2): Gregg Smith Singers - The Founding years, Side 2: Tufts, Walter, Urania, gss_599; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
    Band 1: Standish, Isle of Wight, Psalm 100 new (Tufts); Band 2: Southwell New, Windsor, London Tune, Psalm 148 (Walter); Band 3: Urania; Band 4: Standish, Isle of Wight: 4 versions Cambridge; Bard 4: The Lord descended (Lyon); Band 5: Psalm 119 (Lyon)
  - Art of the Round, side 1, gss_617; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Art of the Round, side 2, gss_618; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Autonomy of Voice, Shuko Mizuno, gss_767; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Baltimore (1), 05/13/1973; gss_824; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Baltimore (2), 05/13/1973; gss_825; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Baltimore (3), 05/13/1973; gss_826; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Samuel] Barber (4), gss_263; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    Slates: 404: "Bridge Game" (orchestra, tenor, soprano; 405: (part of above)
  - [Samuel] Barber; [Douglas] Moore (1), gss_539; Recordings of "A hand of Bridge" an one act opera of Samuel Barber with libretto by Gian Carlo Menotti and "Gallantry", one act opera by Douglas Moore.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    "A hand of Bridge" an one act opera of Samuel Barber, libretto by Gian Carlo Menotti; "Gallantry", on act opera by Douglas Moore
  - [William] Bergsma (10), gss_248; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slate: 1001-1007: "In Marble halls" (mixed choir, more diction); 1008-1009: "Wig wags..." (mixed choir)
  - [William] Bergsma (9), gss_247; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slates: 901-904/906-917: "White bird..." (mixed chorus); 905: "King's white hall" (mixed chorus); 905: "To..." (mixed chorus)
  - [William] Bergsma/Richards (11), gss_249; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slates: 1101-1107: "Wig- wag..." (mixed chorus); 1108: "First take Richards" (mixed chorus, soloists); 1109-1116: ? (mixed chorus, soloists)
  - Bernstein (1): Choruses from "The Lark", gss_906; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
    1. [Leonard] Bernstein - French choruses - #1 + #3
  - Beware (1), gss_827; Could be "Beware of the Soldier" by Gregg Smith; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Beware (2), gss_828; Could be "Beware of the Soldier" by Gregg Smith; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Beware (3), gss_829; Could be "Beware of the Soldier" by Gregg Smith; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Beware (4), gss_830; Could be "Beware of the Soldier" by Gregg Smith; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Beware of the Soldier, gss_783; Note on the box reads: "B: Soldier May 15 Edition".; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 20:30 (Oversize 57)
  - Beware of the Soldier (2), gss_831; Prelim master of "Beware of the Soldier" by Gregg Smith; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [William] Billings: "As the Hart Panteth", 11/03/1975; gss_875; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Marc] Blitzstein: Harpies, gss_537; "Harpies" by Marc Blitzstein performed by tenor, altos, small orchestra, soprano with piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
  - Blue Monday, gss_540; Recording of "Blue Monday", chamber opera by George Gershwin.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
    "Blue Monday", chamber opera by George Gershwin; Sam - Walter Richardson; Mike - Patrick Mason; alto - Priscilla Magdamo; tenors - Jeff Meyer, Thomas Bogdan; soprano solos: Catherine Aks; Joyce Andrews
  - Brimstone (8), gss_246; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
    Slate: 801-805: "Sanctus Sanctus" (contralto, mixed chorus); 806-807/810: "Gloria" (contralto, mixed chorus); 808-809/811-814:"In Excelsis Deo" (contralto, mixed chorus); 815-818: "White Bird..." (contralto, mixed chorus)
  - Britten (2), gss_895; Note on the box reads: "Use small reel switch!".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Benjamin] Britten, 1981; gss_660; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - [Benjamin] Britten: "First day", 11/28/1977; gss_661; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - Bruce Adolph session (2), gss_765; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Butler - Talma (part 1), gss_255; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 20)
  - [Eugene] Butler (1), gss_433; Recording of orchestra, oboe and soprano solos.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    101: (orchestra, oboe solo, soprano solo); 102-108: (orchestra, oboe solo)
  - [Eugene] Butler (2), gss_434; Recording of orchestra, oboe and soprano solos.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    Cont'd from 433: 201-211: (orchestra, oboe, soprano)
  - [Eugene] Butler (3), gss_435; Recording of orchestra, oboe and soprano solos.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    Cont'd from 434: 301-311: (orchestra, oboe, soprano)
  - [Eugene] Butler (4), gss_436; Recording of orchestra, oboe and soprano solos performances with comets.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    Cont'd from 435: 401-413: (orchestra, oboe, soprano)
  - [Eugene] Butler (5), gss_437; Recording of orchestra, oboe and soprano solos.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    Cont'd from 436: 501-511: (orchestra, oboe, soprano)
  - Canticles of Praise, Gregg Smith, 05/01/1968; gss_760; Canticle of Praise, Gregg Smith. Commissioned by St. Andrews Presbyterian College, Laurinburg, North Caroling for the St. Andrews College Choir, Thomas Somerville - director. Premiere Performance - May 1, 1968, Gregg Smith - Conductor; Madeline Leonard - soprano; Judi Lawson - alto; Kent Morgan - tenor; Charles White - bass; John Williams - organ; Virginia Boyce - piano; Patty Hickey - celeste; Lucy Scott, Delia Becton, Shirley Isenhovr - percussion; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
    Side 1: Muts. 1-6; Side 2: Mut. 7
  - Carter; Ravel (2), gss_659; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - [Elliott] Carter - Defense of Corinth, gss_715; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 14:30 (Oversize 55)
  - [Elliott] Carter - Harmonie [sic], gss_716; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 14:30 (Oversize 55)
  - [Elliott] Carter and Tarantella Emblems (1 of 2), gss_714_01; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - [Elliott] Carter and Tarantella Emblems (2 of 2), gss_714_02; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - [Elliott] Carter Music (5), gss_718; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - [Elliott] Carter Music (6), gss_719; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - [Elliott] Carter Music (7), gss_720; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
    Skryabin 6
  - Elliot Carter ("proof copy"), gss_846; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Elliot Carter: "Tarantella"; "Emblems", Gregg Smith Singers, Long Island Choral Society, gss_845; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Elliott Carter Complete, gss_717; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 14:38 (Oversize 55)
    To music (7:05); Heart not so heavy (4:23); Musicians (3:10)
  - Elliott Carter Proof copy, gss_759; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Elliott Carter: "Tarantella"; "Emblems", gss_756; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - A Celebration for Louise: A Concert of the Music of Louise Talma (reel 2), 02/05/1977; gss_785; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    Side 1: 5 - "Voice of Peace" (1973), Gregg Smith Singers (28:25); Side 2: 6 - Announcements; "Four Handed Fun", Lukas Foss and Louise Talma, piano
  - [Paul] Chihara; [William] Bergsma; [Carolyn] Madison; [Donald] Waxman, gss_932; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:18 (SCRC 19:D:1)
    Includes Carolyn Madison: Two Pieces
  - Columbia Univ. Glee Club: "Stopwatch", 01/29/1976; gss_904; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is most likely "A Stopwatch and an Ordnance Map" by Samuel Barber, performed by the Columbia Univ. Men's Glee Club.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Copernicus, 11/16/1973; gss_774; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Copernicus (2), gss_619; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Copernicus II (2), gss_823; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Copland - An Immorality; Thomson - 4 Hymns, gss_035; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - [Henry] Cowell: Luther; [Samuel] Barber: Stopwatch, gss_184; Notes from the audio engineer RJH read: "chorus". Most likely the full titles for the musical pieces are: 1: "Luther's Carol for his Son"; 2: "A Stop Watch and an Ordnance Map"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 14)
  - Dance Music Mariage [sic] Fouse, gss_909; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Daroz (2), gss_431; Recording of oboe and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    Continuation from 430: 201-221: (oboe, soprano)
  - Daroz (3), gss_432; Recording of oboe and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    Continuation from 431: 301-317: (oboe, soprano)
  - Daroz, Oboe-Roz [Rosalind Rees], Darrel Handle (1), gss_430; Recording of oboe and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 33)
    101-109: (oboe, soprano)
  - Dedication (1-4), gss_711; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - Druck, etc. (1), gss_242; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: 101-112: (unaccop. mixed chorus in German)
  - Druck, etc. (2), gss_243; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: 201-206: "Shake up..." (unaccomp. mixed chorus); 207-212: "Call on you..." (soprano, mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - Druck, etc. (3), gss_244; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: 301: "You..." (soprano, chorus); 302-305: "Gone you" (soprano, chorus); 306: "The wheel of Fortune" (soprano, chorus); 307: "You..." (soprano, chorus); 308: "Luck beside you" (soprano, chorus); 309-310: "... upon you..." (soprano, chorus); 311: "The wheel of Fortune" (soprano, chorus); 312-313: "Death be not proud" (mixed chorus)
  - Druck, etc. (4), gss_245; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 18)
    Slates: 401-404: "Death be not proud" (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 405-413: "Get up, get up" (men's chorus, mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - [Jacob] Druckman: "Madrigals", gss_881; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Jacob] Druckman; [William] Schuman; [Michael] Hennegin, gss_933; Two tapes in the same box (gss_933 and gss_934).; 1/4 inch audio tape (SCRC 19:D:1)